全球有1500多万人，超过半数年龄在24岁以下，每天定期观看60秒以内的短视频，包括通过Snapchat、TikTok、Instagram故事以及其他智能手机应用分享的片段。
Mehr als 1,5 Millionen Menschen weltweit, über die Hälfte unter dem Alter von 24 Jahren, schauen regelmäßig kurze Videos, Klips von 60 Sekunden oder weniger, mit Snapchat, TikTok, Instagram-Storys und anderen Smartphone-Apps.
七年前，这个市场几乎不存在。
The market barely existed seven years ago.
然而今天，创作者每天上传7002万条短视频。
Yet today, creators are uploading 702 million short videos every day.
随着我们的注意力下降到秒级，短视频不仅会持续存在，而且将成为新的常态。
As our attention span is falling to seconds, short video is not only here to stay, but will become the new normal.
与其他社交平台如Instagram不同，那里充满了完美编辑过、打磨光洁的图片，而短视频更加易于接触，鼓励不完美和真实性。
Unlike other social platforms such as Instagram, where perfectly edited, polished images are the norm, short videos are more accessible, inviting imperfection and authenticity.
因为每个片段都非常短，因此内容生产者需要具有创意和简洁的沟通技巧。
And because each clip is so short, content producers have to be creative and concise communicators.
但这些小块状视频不仅仅是娱乐，而且还有更多含义。
But these bite-sized videos are more than just fun and entertainment.
对于我个人来说作为一名顾问和母亲，短视频是我获取育儿建议的地方。
For me personally, as a consultant and mother, short videos are where I get parenting tips.
在去上班的路上，我可以快速了解如何在旅行中哺乳的秘密，以及关于让我女儿早点睡觉的优秀想法。
On my way to work, I can quickly learn about the secrets of breastfeeding while travelling and get great ideas about how to make my daughter sleep sooner.
企业也逐渐认识到，短视频是找到新客户和扩大受众多样性的好方法。
Businesses are also learning that short videos is a great way to find new customers and expand the diversity of the audiences.
今年早些时候，我领导了一项项目，与全球领先的短视频平台TikTok合作，评估这种小块经济的经济和社会影响。
Earlier this year, I led a project with TikTok, the world's leading short video platform, to assess the economic and social impact of this bite-sized economy.
我们的研究表明，这个年轻的媒介正在改变我们消磨时间的方式远不止这些。
Our study shows that this young medium is changing a lot more than the way we spend our leisure time.
在2019年，短视频创造了约1200万个全球性工作，并为货物和服务销售带来了估计的950亿美元。
In 2019, Short Video generated an estimated US$95 billion in goods and services sold and created roughly 1.2 million jobs globally.
即使在短暂生命中，短视频已经开始影响我们工作、沟通和学习的方式。
Even within its short lifespan, Short Video is already impacting the way we work, communicate and learn.
在COVID-19大流行期间，当世界各地的博物馆因不必要的接触而关闭时，许多人纷纷转向短视频来快速传播信息并吸引一群新的、年轻的观众。
In der Zeit der COVID-19-Krise, während Museums all over die Welt vor unbedeutendem Umgang sind, haben viele schnell zu bringen und eine neue, jüngere Zuschauer zu engagieren.
佛罗伦萨的乌菲兹画廊，在三年前创建了正式新网站后，利用短视频来发现新的观众欣赏他们的雕像和绘画。
Die Uffizi-Galerie in Florenz, die vor drei Jahren ihre offizielle neue Website erstellt hat, benutzt Short-Videos, um neue Zuschauer zu entdecken für ihre Statuen und Painten.
通过使用表情符号、音乐歌词或幽默元素的展览。
Mit Exhibiten mit Emojis, Musik-Lyrics oder witzigen Wurzeln.
这个博物馆使艺术作品更具可访问性和相关性，为年轻一代的艺术爱好者带来新的体验。
Das Museum macht das Kunstwerk mehr accessibel und relevant für die jüngere Generation der Kunst-Liebenden.
在其最后一条帖子中，一只猫头像被分成两半，一个带有冠状病毒的摇滚卡片放在了卡瓦贾艺术家墨达莎的作品前，这个作品有权力将那些注视着它的人转化为石头。
In einem seiner letzten Posts wurde ein Katzen-Coronavirus in eine Rock-Karte getrennt und in der Hälfte geschlagen, vor Karavajas Kunstwerk Medusa, die die Macht hat, diejenigen, die auf sie in Stahl schauen, zu turnieren.
乌菲兹还在一款短视频平台上与名人进行了直播实验，让全球观众体验到他们从未亲眼见过的画廊景象。
Uffizi hat auch mit Influencers Live-Streaming von der Galerie auf einer kurzen Videoplattform experimentiert, um die Zuschauer weltweit zu erleben, was sie in Person noch nie gesehen haben.
自从4月份在TikTok获得关注以来，仅在三个月内，这家博物馆的社交账号吸引了4万3千多粉丝。
Seit seiner Aufmerksamkeit auf TikTok im April 2020 hat die Profile des Museums mehr als 43.000 Follower in drei Monaten getragen.
与在Twitter上建立的四年内类似的粉丝基础相比，这个博物馆在TikTok上的发展速度要快得多。
Die Geschwindigkeit ist viel schneller als ihre Reise auf Twitter, in der es in den letzten vier Jahren ein ähnliches Niveau von Fanbase gebaut hat.
小型企业也利用短视频作为发现可能从未听说过他们或他们产品的人群的方式。
Small businesses are also using short video as a way to find new audiences who might have never heard of them or their products before.
在2018年，作为中国短视频平台领军人物之一的抖音，在履行社会责任中为了缓解中国贫困问题，启动了一项帮助中国高山地区个体农民和小企业自主生产的活动。
In 2018, Douyin, the leading Chinese short video platform, as part of its social responsibility initiative to alleviate poverty in China, launched a campaign to help individual farmers and small businesses in China's mountainous areas self-farm produce.
作为其试点项目之一，抖音邀请内容生产者制作四个15秒的短视频，展示他们产品的优质。
As one of its pilot projects, Douyin invited content producers to create four pieces of 15-second short videos, showcasing the quality of their products.
此外，还有其他常规的公关活动，如推广文章。
This is on top of other regular PR initiatives such as promotional articles.
他们希望利用短视频的庞大用户群，为那些可能对这些产品感兴趣的人找到客户，然后将他们与电商网站连接起来，使人们在观看视频时可以购买商品。
They wanted to leverage the large user base of short video to find those customers who might be interested in those products and then connected them with the e-commerce website so that people can buy things as they watch the videos.
仅用五天时间，这项倡议帮助四千多家四川省家庭销售了令人惊讶的12万公斤杏子。
In just five days, the initiative helped nearly 4,000 families in Sichuan province sell an astonishing 120,000 kg of plums.
许多对年轻人养育和关注感兴趣的品牌将短视频作为一种新鲜方式来吸引世纪Z代用户。
Viele Brands, die interessiert sind in die Haltung und die Betreuung von jungen Leuten, haben Short Videos als frische Weise, um mit Generation Z zu engagieren.
比如说，麦当劳的竞争对手中有超过一半的人在16到24岁之间。
Zum Beispiel sind mehr als eine Hälfte der McDonalds-Kompeten zwischen 16 und 24 Jahre alt.
在过去的几年里，澳大利亚的餐厅行业在招募新员工方面取得了显著成绩。
In Australien stammte die Branche in den vergangenen Jahren zu rekrutieren.
因此，他们推出了一个名为Snapchat应用的东西。
So launchierte sie etwas namens Snapchat-Applikation.
这是一款Snapchat长度的应用，向客户推送10秒视频展示他们为什么是完美的麦当劳员工，然后发送招聘网站链接。
Das ist eine Snapchat-Länge, die den Kunden zehn Sekunden Videos schiebt, die zeigen, warum sie einen perfekten McDonalds-Employee sind und dann den Link-Job-Applikationen schicken.
在这次活动启动后的24小时内，麦当劳收到了3000份Snapchat申请。
In 24 Stunden nach dem Launchen der Kampagne bekam McDonalds 3.000 Snapchat-Applikationen.
这一天比传统方法整周带来的申请多4倍。
viermal mehr als die Zahl, die sie die ganze Woche mit traditionellen Methoden bekommen haben.
尚不清楚短视频是不是最好的找到合适人选或挖掘人才的方式。
Es ist unklar, ob ein kurzes Video das beste Weg ist, die richtigen Leute für den Job zu finden oder Talent zu retten.
但通过他们招募的人数来看，这场活动在全球范围内是一次巨大成功。
Aber nur durch die Numeren, die sie rekrutiert haben, war die Kampagne ein globaler Hitsch.
在沙特阿拉伯，麦当劳在24小时内收到了4.3万份Snack应用。
In Saudi-Arabien hat McDonalds 43.000 Snack-Applikationen in 24 Stunden bekommen.
该公司后来又在美国重新启动了这场活动。
und die Firma eröffnete die Kampagne wieder, später in den USA.
无论如何，我想从短视频育儿中得到一些建议。
Wie auch immer, möchte ich von Short Video Parenthood Tipps bekommen.
许多观众也希望学习这款平台，但是在小块、更大的剂量中。
Viele Zuschauer wollen auch, die Plattform zu lernen, aber in einer kleinen, größeren Dosis.
在我们的研究中，全球短视频观众将会把这款平台的顶级优点排列起来，包括发现新兴趣和新技能。
In unserer Studie werden Short Video Zuschauer global die Top-Benefiz der Plattform rankieren, als neue Interessen und neue Fähigkeiten zu entdecken.
在相当大的市场中，短视频对于教育和学习领域具有巨大的潜力，可以改变现状。
In der erheblichen Marktart besonders, das kurze Video für Lehre und Bildung hat große Potenziale, die Status quo zu verändern.
在2019年，TikTok在印度启动了一场旨在实现印度数字社区民主教育的活动。
In 2019 launchte TikTok eine Kampagne in Indien mit dem Ziel der demokratisierten Unterrichtung für die indische digitale Gemeinschaft.
尽管自2020年7月起在某些国家被禁止使用，但TikTok已经为创意短视频建立了庞大的人群调查，并填补了其他平台的空白。
Während die App seit Juli 2020 in den Ländern gebannt ist, hat sie eine große Befragung für kreative, kurze Video-Kontakte eröffnet und andere Plattformen in den Raum gefüllt sind.
通过与印度的社会开发者、创业公司和受欢迎的创作者合作，TikTok实现了这一趋势。他们共同制作了15秒的小视频，涉及各种主题。
TikTok konnte diesen Trend erzielen, indem sie mit indischen Sozialentwicklern, Start-ups, und populären Kreatoren zusammenarbeiten, um 15 Sekunden kurze Videos zu produzieren, die eine Reihe von Themen covern.
从学校级别的科学到学习新语言。
Von Schule-Level-Science bis zu neuen Sprachen zu lernen.
随着短视频在平台上的广泛传播，观众受到了启发，有些甚至开始创作自己的教育内容。
As the first wave of short video became widely spread on the platform, audiences got inspired, and some even began to create their own educational content.
到2019年10月，这场活动已经产生了超过1000万个短视频，共获得4800亿次观看。
By October 2019, the campaign had generated more than 10 million videos and garnered 48 billion views.
通过帮助人们学习并参与内容创作过程，短视频实际上正在培养和训练具备应对未来挑战能力的人才群体。
Through helping people learn and participate into the process of content creation, short videos are in fact helping prep and train the skilled population that can take on the challenges of the future.
就像所有社交媒体一样，对于短视频平台也存在合理的担忧。
Like all social media, there are valid concerns around short video platforms.
包括数据隐私、这种格式的上瘾特性以及内容缺乏涵义和背景信息。
Including data privacy, the addictive nature of the format, and the lack of nuance and context in the content.
不过，我仍然认为短视频的正面影响会超过其不足之处。
However, I still think that the positive outcomes of short video will outweigh its downsize.
我相信，未来的经济和社会力量中，短视频将变得更加重要。
I believe short video will become a more vital economic and social force in the future.
正是因为如此，我们需要找到正确的方法，在用户、平台和决策者之间进行合作，以便从这个年轻的媒体中获益。
It is precisely because of this that we need to find the right way to benefit from this young medium through collaboration among users, platforms and policy makers.
谢谢。
Thank you.